Maurice Neufeld Additional Files /4230
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Persistence sources, A-Kn. (Box 24)
  - Persistence Sources H-J (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Persistence Sources K-Kn1, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Persistence sources, Kn-Ph. (Box 25)
  - Persistence Sources Kn 2 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Persistence Sources Kn3 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Persistence Sources Kn 4, 1834 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Persistence Sources kn5, 1880 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Persistence Sources La-Lo, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Persistence Sources Lp-Lz (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Persistence Sources M-Mi, 1836 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Persistence Sources Mo1 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Persistence Sources Mo2-Mz, 1830 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Persistence Sources N-Nat1, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Persistence Sources Nat 2, 1863 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Persistence Sources Nat 3, 1864 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Persistence Sources Nat 4, 1860 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Persistence Sources Nat 5-6, 1860 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Persistence Sources Nat 7, 1860-1900 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Persistence Sources Nat-Ph (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Persistence sources, Po-Z. (Box 26)
  - Persistence Sources Po-Pz (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Persistence Sources Q- So1 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Persistence Sources Sz, 1834 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Persistence Sources T-Un1, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Persistence Sources Un 2, 1836 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Persistence Sources Un3-z (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Labor Agreements, 1791-1900 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Labor Agreements, 1901-1915 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Labor Agreements, 1916-1980 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - U.S Industrial Commission, 1898-1901 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - U.S Industrial Commission, 1898-1901 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Blair Hearings, 1883-1886 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Persistence Folder 1, 1830 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Persistence Folder 1, 1830 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- ILR courses 200-430. (Box 27)
  - ILR 200 I Labor History, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - ILR 200 II Labor History, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - ILR 200 C-1, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - ILR 200 C-2, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - ILR 200 C-3, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - ILR 200 C-4, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - ILR 200 C-5, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - ILR 200 C-6, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - ILR 301, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - ILR 430-1, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - ILR 200 430-2, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - ILR 200 430-3, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - ILR 200 430-4, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - ILR 200 430-5, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - ILR 200 430-6, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - ILR 200 430-7, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - ILR 200 430-8, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- ILR courses 431-604. (Box 28)
  - ILR 431-1, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - ILR 431-2, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - ILR 431-3, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - ILR 431-4, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - ILR 431/531-1, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - ILR 431/531-2, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - ILR 431/531-3, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - ILR 431/531-4, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - ILR 431/531-5, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - ILR 431/531-6, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - ILR 604-1, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - ILR 604-2, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - ILR 604-3, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - ILR 604-4, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - ILR 604-5, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - ILR 604-6, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- ILR courses 604-702. (Box 29)
  - ILR 604-7, 1922 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - ILR 605-1, 1922 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - ILR 605-2, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - ILR 606-1, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - ILR 606-2, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - ILR 606-3, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - ILR 606-4, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - ILR 606-5, 1835 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - ILR 606-6, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - ILR 606-7, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - ILR 606-8, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - ILR 606-9 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - ILR 606-10 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - ILR 702-1, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - ILR 702-2, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - ILR 702-3, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- ILR courses 702 and additional sources. (Box 30)
  - ILR 702-4, 1860-1880 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - ILR 702-5, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - ILR 702-6, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - ILR 702-7, 1920 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - ILR 702-8 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - The Problems of the skilled workers (UAW), 1959 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - UAW (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - ILGWU, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Henry Fond II (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Warren Moscow History of Local 3, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Meyer Bernstein the steelworkers Election, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Thomas W. Holland National Labor Policy by Agreement (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Thomas W. Holland National Labor Policy by Agreement (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Union Democracy Review (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Local 3 Internation Brotherhood of E.W, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Agricultural Labor (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Labor Union Periodicals (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Knights of Labor Haymarket, 1885-1886 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Ethnic Labor Coalition (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Labor union membership, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Italian Clipping and Article file (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Union Democracy Review, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Entertainment Industry Unions (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - MS History of the United Automobile Workers By David Billmyer (Box 30, Folder 24)